Finding Aid for John Lesinski papers, 1930s-1964
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual materials
  - Motion pictures, probably from campaign, 1964; 3 film reels Super 16 mm (Box 27)
  - Campaign posters (Folder 1)